VADIM TRYBAY

Python backend and JavaScript full-stack developer

CONTACTS

+38 (096) 567-86-67

user0606user@gmail.com

Linkedin

GitHub

Portfolio

<u>Telegram</u>

Bucharest, Romania

TECH SKILLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Django
- FastApi
- Flask
- React
- Angular
- PotgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- Git
- OOP
- · Scrapy, BS4
- HTML/CSS
- Docker

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Conscientiousness
- Responsibility
- Desire to learn
- Problem solving
- Optimism
- Critical thinking

LANGUAGES

- English Pre-intermediate
- Ukrainian Native

SUMMARY

Motivated Python and JavaScript software developer, constantly learning and improving my skills. Studied a wide range of technologies, including web frameworks such as FastAPI, Django, React, Angular and Flask. Experienced with database management systems such as MySQL, PostgreSQL and MongoDB, as well as message brokers such as RabbitMQ. Proficient in HTML5 and CSS to create attractive user interfaces. Seeks to use my knowledge and contribute to effective team projects.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Django project "nasha-firma.od.ua" | Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

This project is a real website on the Internet, which was carried out for the purpose of training and helping my friends in the development and maintenance of business.

FastApi project "nasha-firma" | Jan 2024 - Feb 2024

Already implemented functionality FastApi:

- this is a good Fastapi project
- error handler
- healthchecker for check DB status
- authentication JWT mechanism
- · forget password mechanism

FastApi project "LLM Chat Bot" | Oct 2023 - Jan 2024

Developed a convenient personal chatbot: "LLM Chat Bot,". This innovative tool not only reads and recognizes documents but also features voice recognition for natural interactions. "LLM Chat Bot". This project uses technologies such as: FastAPI, Streamlit, PostgresSQL, Docker, OpenAI, Speech2Text, Faiss, Git, LangChain, Cloudinary, Redis, YoutubeVideoLoader.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance website development

"nasha-firma.od.ua" | November 2023 - May 2024

- using the Django framework
- using PostrgeSQL database
- authentication and authorization

Lead developer: development from start to finish

Junior Python development

"Tekra" | May 2024 - now

- using the PyQt6
- using FastApi framework
- using Angular framework
- work with robotic processes
- developer assistant: desktop application development

EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

JavaScript Fullstack Developer | February 2024 - July 2024

IT School GoIT

Python Web Developer | October 2022 - July 2023 Python Data Science | July 2023 - November 2023

IT School Hillel

Python Core | August 2022 - October 2022

OGAU

Master's degree in agronomy | August 2000 - July 2004